lovelearnings.com 2018-03-23

# Privacy Policy

_If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email  info@lovelearnings.com._

This privacy policy sets out how [www.lovelearnings.com](http://www.lovelearnings.com/) (owned by LoveLearnings Media Inc) uses and protects any information that you provide when you use this website.

LoveLearnings Media Inc (“LoveLearnings”) is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

LoveLearnings may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you agree with any changes.

**This policy was last revised:  July 4th, 2017**

* * *

### **Information We May Collect**

We may collect the following personally identifiable information if you complete a quiz, subscribe to our newsletter or email series, download a free e-book or PDF report, submit a comment on an article or post, or fill out a contact form.

  * gender
  * email address
  * message details you send with contact or comment inquiries
  * all answers you provide in the quizzes on this website
  * anonymous quiz ID number associated with your quiz results report

### **What Additional Information Do We Collect?**

Our servers automatically recognize visitors’ domain names and IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet). No personal information about you is revealed in this process.

### **What We May Do With the Information We Gather**

We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent. If you leave our website and purchase a product or service we promote, the company you purchase from will notify us of the purchase as well as certain identifying information for you. We do not share this information with others.

We may use the information you provide to better understand your needs and provide you with a better experience.  We may also use your personal information for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * We may email you your quiz results score or results report link.
  * From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes.
  * We may contact you by email.
  * We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### **What are “cookies” / “clear GIFs” and how do we use them?**

Cookies: Like many other commercial sites, our Site utilizes standard technologies called “cookies” and clear GIFs to collect information about how our Site is used. A cookie is a small data text file, which a website stores on your computer’s hard drive (if your web browser permits) that can later be retrieved to identify you to us.

Cookies were designed to help a website recognize a user’s browser as a previous visitor and thus save and remember any preferences that may have been set while the user was browsing the site. A cookie cannot be read by a website other than the one that set the cookie. A cookie cannot pass on a computer virus or capture any of the Personally Identifiable Information that resides on your computer.

Clear GIFs: At times, we work with third-party service partners that employ clear GIFs (also known as pixel tags, single pixel GIFs, web beacons or action tags) for our benefit to help us measure advertising effectiveness. Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of our users. The main difference between the two is that clear GIFs are invisible on the page and are much smaller, about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. Clear GIFs are not tied to your Personally Identifiable Information and only track the visitor traffic and behavior to and on our Site.

Clear GIFs can “work with” existing cookies on a computer if they are both from the same website or advertising company. That means, for example, that if a person visited “www.companyX.com”, which uses an advertising company’s clear GIF, the website would match the clear GIFs identifier and the advertising company’s cookie ID number, to show the past online behavior for that computer. This collected information can be shared with the advertising company.

### How do we store your information?

If you have taken a quiz, information about your quiz answers and results is stored in a database on our server.  This information is identified by a unique ID number, which may be associated with your email address (if you choose to provide one, as it is optional and your quiz data will remain anonymous if you choose not to enter an email address).

Your information is stored at the list server that delivers our newsletters. Your information can only be accessed by those who help manage those lists in order to deliver e-mail newsletters.

All of the newsletters that are sent to you include an unsubscribe link in them at the very bottom. You may unsubscribe at any time by clicking that link.

You can remove yourself at any time from our mailing lists to prevent any further automated emails sent from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link. You can also contact us at [info@lovelearnings.com](mailto:info@lovelearnings.com) to change your information or unsubscribe at any time.

### **Links To Other Websites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

* * *

**If you have any questions or concerns, please email[info@lovelearnings.com](mailto:info@lovelearnings.com).**

LoveLearnings Media Inc  
300-1095 McKenzie Ave  
Victoria, BC  V8P2L5  
Canada
